Extinction will find you.
The Thaw is a horror, science fiction film directed by Mark A. Lewis.
At a remote Arctic research station, four ecology students discover the real horror of
global warming is not the melting ice, but what's frozen within it.
A prehistoric parasite is released from the carcass of a Woolly Mammoth upon the unsuspecting students who are
forced to quarantine and make necessary sacrifices, or risk infecting the rest of the world.
Dr. David Kruipen, played by Val Kilmer.
Evelyn Kruipen, played by Martha MacIsaac.
Atom Galen, played by Aaron Ashmore.
Federico Fulce, played by Kyle Schmid.
Bart, played by Viv Leacock.
Ling Chen, played by Steph Song.
The Thaw is a 2009 American science fiction horror
thriller film directed by Mark A.
Lewis and starring Val Kilmer, Martha MacIsaac, and Aaron Ashmore.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.